<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Yash Tandon</title><link>https://itsyash.fun/</link><description>Recent content on Yash Tandon</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://itsyash.fun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cilium Wars: Scaling Up Your Network with Jedi-like Cilium Handling Techniques</title><link>https://itsyash.fun/posts/2023/02/cilium-wars-scaling-up-your-network-with-jedi-like-cilium-handling-techniques/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://itsyash.fun/posts/2023/02/cilium-wars-scaling-up-your-network-with-jedi-like-cilium-handling-techniques/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re working with Kubernetes, chances are you&amp;rsquo;ve heard of Cilium, a popular networking and security solution for Kubernetes that provides efficient and secure network connectivity between services. However, as your cluster grows in size, managing Cilium becomes a challenge. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore some best practices and techniques for scaling up your network with Jedi-like Cilium handling techniques.
Understanding Cilium Architecture Before we dive into handling Cilium at scale, let&amp;rsquo;s understand the architecture of Cilium.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://itsyash.fun/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://itsyash.fun/about/</guid><description>Hey, I&amp;rsquo;m Yash, a Senior DevOps engineer at Sprinklr. When I&amp;rsquo;m not working on Kubernetes, distributed systems, DevOps, observability, or Open Source, you can find me playing the drums and listening to some good old rock music. AC/DC and Green Day are my all-time favorite bands, and their music inspires me to tackle complex technical challenges with the same energy and intensity they bring to their performances. I&amp;rsquo;m also a big fan of Real Madrid and enjoy playing FIFA like a pro.</description></item><item><title>Books and Books</title><link>https://itsyash.fun/bookshelf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://itsyash.fun/bookshelf/</guid><description>Welcome to my Digital Library! These are All Books that i currently own - I have broadly divided them into tech and non-tech, if you think i should checkout some other book as well reach out to me!
Read Tech Site Reliability Engineering Book Site Reliability Workbook Accelerate: Building and Scaling High Performing Technology Organisations Clean Code The Clean Coder System Design Interview Personal Finance / Self Improvement The Psychology of Money: Timeless Lessons on Wealth, Greed, and Happiness Coffee Can Investing Good Economics for Hard Times Currently Reading Tech Software Architecture: The Hard Parts Designing Data Intensive Applications</description></item></channel></rss>